A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Publications, Working Files and Photographs FA1394
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Photographs, 1968-1993; 2; 1.75 Cubic Feet 5 containers
  - Ford Foundation 1991 Annual Report - "Expenditures"...Revised - Use this disk for this chart, disregard chart on other disk (Box 27, Folder 276)
  - 1992 Annual Report Idea File (Box 27, Folder 277)
  - Annual Report Photos - To Be Refiled, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 278)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government - Exhibit and Poster Slides, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 530)
    Slide titles:
    Panel 4: Environmental Clean Up, Wichita, Kansas, Lynn Johnson
    Panel 6: Quincy Court, Lynn Johnson
    Panel 7: NYC Sanitation Department, Mechanic Tests Engine, David H. Wells, circa 1992
    Panel 8: Woman Working, Machine Shop, Rochester, NY, David H. Wells, circa 1992
    Panel 11: Worker's Comp, David Butow
  - Program-Related Investment (PRI) Exhibit (with Negatives) (3 folders), 1988 (Box 53, Folder 531-533)
    Photos/negatives:
    Folder 531: Pride Gardens
    Children's Playroom, Family Advocacy Project, Ground Floor
    Bedford Stuyvesant Commercial Core Area - Improvement Map
    PRI
    Big Apple Circus
    Tri-House Movers, Watts Labor Community Action Committee
    Watts House Auction
    Film Forum
    3 images from George Griffin's Flying Fur, on view at Film Forum 1 as part of a program of New Animation: Feb. 17-Mar. 2, 1982
    Film Forum - Reporters
    Film Forum - The Atomic Cafe
    The Judge and the Assassin still
    Liten Ida (Growing Up)
    Folder 532: Pride Gardens, Mississippi Action for Community Education (MACE)
    Studio Museum in Harlem
    Studio Museum in Harlem - Before and after space + piece of sculpture (separate) + Bearden (separate)
    Chicanos Por La Causa, Amistad program
    Program for the Introduction and Adaptation of Contraceptive Technology (PIACT)
    Folder 533: New York Shakespeare Festival
    YWCA of Jersey City
    Boricua College
    Grameen Bank Project
    Restoration Development Corporation Commercial Center, Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation
    Savannah Landmark Rehabilitation Project
    Spanish Speaking Unity Council
    Artisans Cooperative
  - Ford Foundation Letter - Photos and Art, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 534)
  - Ford Foundation August Letter - Photos and Art, 1987 August (Box 53, Folder 535)
  - Ford Foundation June Letter - Photos and Art, 1987 June (Box 53, Folder 536)
  - Ford Foundation December Letter - Photos and Art, 1987 December (Box 53, Folder 537)
  - Ford Foundation October Letter - Photos and Art, 1987 August-October (Box 53, Folder 538)
  - Ford Foundation August Letter - Photos and Art, 1987 August (Box 53, Folder 539)
    The Youth Project - Minneapolis, Minnesota
    #1-8 Indian Woman Doing Bead Work for Craft Business
    #9-35 Illinois Neighborhood Development, South Shore Bank, Housing Rehabilitation Work
  - Ford Foundation June Letter - Photos and Art, 1987 June (Box 53, Folder 540)
  - Ford Foundation Letter Photos, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 541)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, 1957-1985 (Box 53, Folder 542)
    Photos include:
    United Nations Headquarters
    Whitney M. Young, Jr. portrait, Urban League
    Roy Wilkins portrait
    Martin Luther King, Jr. portrait
    Group Photo
    Low Memorial Library and Plaza, Columbia University
    Aerial Campus Shot, University of Chicago
  - Possible Annual Report Photos, undated (Box 53, Folder 543)
    American Repertory Theatre - "The King Stag"
    Wayang Wong, Court Art of Java, Festival of Indonesia, Photo: Jack Vartoogian
    Festival of Indonesia, Court Art of Java from the Kraton of Yogyakarta in "Bedhoyo", Photo by Rachel Cooper
    Festival of Indonesia, Court Art of Java from the Kraton of Yogyakarta in "Bedhaya", Photo by Linda Vartoogian
  - Franklin A. Thomas Information Packet with Photographs, 1979 January 30 (Box 54, Folder 544)
    Includes:
    Biographical sketch of Franklin A. Thomas
    Ford Foundation Chronology
    Ford Foundation Highlights, 1966-1979 - I. Domestic, II. International, III. Institutional
    Press Release - Franklin Thomas named seventh president of the Ford Foundation, Jan. 30, 1979
    Past Presidents of the Ford Foundation